<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tori Code</title>
    <link>https://toricode.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tori Code</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 23:58:56 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://toricode.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Write Excel File using xlwt</title>
      <link>https://toricode.com/python-write-excel-file-using-xlwt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 23:58:56 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toricode.com/python-write-excel-file-using-xlwt/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial we will learn how to use xlwt package to write Excel file in Python.
Install xlwt package Firstly you need to install xlwt package by command below.
pip install xlwt Create Workbook and Sheet Import xlwt package import xlwt
First step to write Excel file we need to create workbook and add a new sheet. workbook = xlwt.Workbook() sheet = workbook.add_sheet(&amp;#34;contacts&amp;#34;)
Create cell style Below example code to create style for header cell with bold text and Arial font.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Read Excel File using xlrd</title>
      <link>https://toricode.com/python-read-excel-file-using-xlrd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 20:27:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toricode.com/python-read-excel-file-using-xlrd/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial we will learn how to read Excel file in Python using xlrd package.
Install xlrd package Firstly you need to install xlrd package by command below.
pip install xlrd Read Excel Spreadsheet in Python To write code example we assump that you have the sample.xlsx Excel file with content as below in your machine.
Below is Python code example to read sample.xlsx Excel file content and sprint the content to terminal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Write Text File</title>
      <link>https://toricode.com/python-write-text-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 14:37:23 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toricode.com/python-write-text-file/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial we will learn how to use Python to write text file with different mode to overwrite or append existing file and how to write Unicode charater to a text file.
Append content to the end of existing file with mode &amp;lsquo;a&amp;rsquo; For example we have the file named test.txt with content as below and located in the same folder of your Python code.
To append to existing file&amp;rsquo;s content we use &amp;lsquo;a&amp;rsquo; for mode argument when open file for writing in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Read Text File</title>
      <link>https://toricode.com/python-read-text-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 22:37:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toricode.com/python-read-text-file/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial we will learn how to use Python to read a text file with different approach of writing code.
Create test text file First step we need to create a text file named test.txt in the same folder that we will create Python code file and input below text for testing purpose.
Hello! from toricode.com This file to test Python text file reading. Happy Coding! Read all text of file To read file in Python we use built-in method open().</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>